<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KochiMyMetro</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metrofare">metrofare</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metrotrains">metrotrains</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metro_about">MetroAbout</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Kochi Metro.\n\n"

        "The introduction of the Metro Rail is expected to change the entire face of Kochi with  "
        "the residents of Kochi having quicker and better access to their jobs, business,education,"
        "livelihood, entertainment and other social activities..\n\n"

        "The strategic goal of the Kochi Metro Rail project is to increase the quality of life of "
        "Kochi citizens by providing mobility to large numbers of people to reach their "
        "destinations in a short span of time. Its main aim is to encourage the residents of Kochi"
        "to use a more economic and eco-friendly alternative to public transport thereby reducing "
        "overcrowding, traffic congestion, transit time as well as the noise and air pollution "
        "caused by the ever growing traffic of Kochi.\n\n"

        "The Kochi Metro app by Citrus Informatics aims to augment this project by helping people "
        "travelling by the metro, find their way around Kochi very easily.You no longer need to "
        " ask anyone for directions to places you want to go to. While waiting for your station to "
        "approach, you can quickly find the restaurants, hospitals, movies and even ATMs near "
        "your station.\n\n"



        "And if you are travelling by road and want to get on the metro, the app can help you find "
        "the nearest metro station. And what's more - you can get to know the tentative fare "
        "information to your destination, distance between the stations and the number of "
        "intermediate stations.\n\n"
        "Just like the metro helps transport people faster, the Kochi metro app helps people find "
        "and reach their destinations faster.\n\n"


    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metrosmartcard">Metrosmartcard</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metroticket">Metroticket</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metropassenger">Metropassenger</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metrostations">Metrostations</string>
</resources>
